Wyatt Earp's Revenge is a western, drama film directed by Michael Feifer.
Wyatt Earp is approached by a journalist for an
interview about how he became a famous sheriff.
Earp told the story of how he was a fearless U.S.
If 27-year old Wyatt Earp comes out that his first
girlfriend Dora Hand was murdered.
Together with his friend Doc Holliday, Bat Masterson, Bill Tilghman and
Charlie Bassett he goes hunting for the perpetrator ...
Wyatt Earp, played by Val Kilmer.
Young Wyatt Earp, played by Shawn Roberts.
Bat Masterson, played by Matt Dallas.
James 'Spike' Kenedy, played by Daniel Booko.
Charlie Bassett, played by Scott Whyte.
Sam Kenedy, played by Steven Grayhm.
Wyatt Earp's Revenge is a 2012 American Western film
about the legendary lawman Wyatt Earp.
It is a fictionalized account of an actual Old West event, the slaying of beautiful
singer Dora Hand in Dodge City, Kansas, when Earp was a deputy there.
In one of its many instances of dramatic license, the
movie depicts Hand as Earp's sweetheart.
The film's framing device is a reporter's interview with an
aging Earp, who reminisces about the tragedy.
(Val Kilmer plays the older Earp, while Shawn Roberts plays the younger one.)
The film was released on March 6, 2012, in the United States.
The film was produced by Jeff Schenck and Barry
Barnholtz and directed by Michael Feifer.
The screenplay was written by Darren Benjamin Shepherd.
The tone is emotional.